翻译，时间轴，压制：Bolshevik0
What do unicorn sweaters, a Quantum destabilizer and sock operas have in common?
独角兽毛衣 量子紊乱制造器和袜子歌剧之间有什么共同点吗
Absolutely nothing.
一点也没有
Unless you're in Gravity Falls. Of course.
当然啦 除非你看的是怪诞小镇
Hi I'm Alyssa with Channel Frederator and we're here to check out even more facts.
大家好 我是Channel Frederator的Alyssa 现在我们来看看还有哪些事实
This is 107 more more facts about Gravity Falls.
这里是关于怪诞小镇的107个更多更多的事实的节目
Don't forget to subscribe and click the bell icon to become part of the notification squad.
别忘了订阅并点击钟形图标来及时收到更新提醒
After three years, two seasons and 40 episodes
三年两季四十集之后
Gravity Falls came to an end on February 15th 2016.
怪诞小镇终于在2016.02.15完结了
Mabel and Dipper ended their crazy and memorable summer at the Mystery Shack.
Mabel和Dipper结束了他们在神秘小屋度过的疯狂却难忘的暑假
注:
Dipper和Mabel的生日是8月31日
Just in time to celebrate their 13th birthdays.
恰好来得及去庆祝他们的13岁生日
The last episode of the series was written back in 2015, about a year before the finale aired.
最后一集的剧本在动画大结局播出的前一年也就是2015年就写好了
Since animation is such a slow process, trader Alex Hirsch had time to deal with the show ending
因为制作动画是一个漫长的过程 制片人Alex Hirsch有时间来处理动画的结局
as he knew there would not be a third season.
意味着他不打算制作第三季
In fact, Hirsch originally didn't want to make any more episodes after the first season.
事实上 Hirsch一开始都不想制作第二季
He had written every episode of season 1 before the first episode had even aired.
在第一季播出之前 他都把第一季的剧本全都写好了
I was concerned that people wouldn't like the show.
我确信没人喜欢这个动画
Luckily, Hirsch's friends Patrick McHale creator of Over the Garden Wall
幸运的是 Hirsch的朋友 花园墙外的制作人Patrick McHale
and Jon Stewart encouraged him to continue the show for a second season.
还有囧司徒建议他继续制作第二季
He couldn't have left season 1 on such a cliffhanger.
他不能就这样留下第一季的悬念
For a long time Hirsch wasn't even allowed to let anyone know
很长一段时间以来 Hirsch甚至都不让别人知道
that Gravity Falls was only going to be two seasons.
怪诞小镇有两季的制作计划
Hirsch put together a live-action alternate reality game called Cipher Hunt,
Hirsch参与制作了一个叫Cipher Hunt的AR游戏
which ran from July 20th through August 2nd of 2016.
从2016年7月20日持续到2016年的8月2日
The goal of Cipher Hunt was to find a statue of Bill Cipher
Cipher Hunt的目标是
by finding and decoding Clues hidden all over the world.
通过在全世界各地寻找密码和解密的方法找到Bill Cipher的雕像
The first players to the statue receive the prize.
最早找到雕像的人将获得奖励
But Hirsch argued that the hunt was more about the journey than a destination.
但是Hirsch也说寻找的过程远比找到后的奖励要重要
Some of the locations players visit along the way are
玩家找到雕像的位置有
the Kazan Cathedral in Saint Petersburg, Russia and Griffith Park in Los Angeles.
俄罗斯圣彼得堡的喀山主教座堂 洛杉矶的格里斐斯公园
The first few locations of the hunt made the shape of Dipper's birthmark, the Big Dipper, when connected together.
最初找到的几个位置连在一起就是Dipper的胎记北斗七星
For one prize during the hunt, fans could decipher a username and password
Cipher Hunt的其中一种奖励是通过解码得到一组用户名和密码
注:
神秘网站http://themysteryofgravityfalls.com/pilot
用户名:
RETURNBACKWARDS
密码:
TOTHEPASTAGAINTHREE
b站版av5870687
that allowed him to sign on to a secret website and view the unaired original pilot for Gravity Falls.
允许玩家进入到一个神秘的网站观看未播出的怪诞小镇最初版试映片
The unaired pilot followed much of the same plot of Tourist Trapped
未播出的试映片剧情和Tourist Trapped 基本一致
but with altered dialogue and wildly different character in art design.
但是对话风格和人物的美术设计完全不同
It's an interesting look into what the show could have been.
观看这个动画的一种可能存在确实很有趣
Hirsch created the pilot in 2010 right after he graduated from Cal Arts
Hirsch在2010年他刚从加州艺术学院毕业的时候制作了这个试映片
by drawing most of the storyboard on post-it notes.
不过大多数分镜都是画在便利贴上面
Disney then rush-ordered the pilot from the studio where he was working at the time,
迪士尼之后火速预订了这个试映片 并由Hirsch所在的工作室的制作
a low-budget flash animation joint in Canada.
这个工作室是一个加拿大低成本flash动画公司
This pilot was only 12 minutes after what a regular Gravity Falls episode would be.
这个试映片只有12分钟 短于普通的一集怪诞小镇
Listen to Wendy and Soos not making the final cut or the mysterious Journal 3.
没有Wendy和Soos的剧情 没有片尾 也没有神秘的日志3的部分
Instead Dipper reads Dr. Crackpot's Book of the Dead
而Dipper读的是疯子博士的死者之书
which to be fair sounds like a pretty wild book.
说实话应该是本有趣的书
In Tourist Trapped Dipper picks out his iconic blue pine tree hat.
在Tourist Trapped 那集中 Dipper挑选了那个标志性的蓝色松树帽
But this pilot shows Dipper wearing his hat throughout the episode.
但是这个试映片显示Dipper一整集都戴着这个帽子
Hirsch has spoken many times about the autobiographical nature of the show.
Hirsch说过很多次这个动画的自传性质
Besides the biggest inspiration as the dynamic between him and his twin sister Ariel.
还有就是他和他姐姐Ariel之间的关系是制作动画最重要的灵感
Every summer they were forced to visit the relatives out in the middle of nowhere.
每个暑假他们都被迫去访问某地中部的亲戚家
With no internet, TV or fun around for miles.
没有互联网 电视 甚至四周都没什么好玩的东西
This encouraged them to use their imaginations to fill the void
这激励着他们运用自身的想象力去填补空白
and created a strong sibling bond.
并且建立起一个强大的双胞胎姐弟关系
For the monster of the week format, Hirsch drew on his childhood obsession with the X-Files.
同样也是一周一个反派的模式 X档案是Hirsch童年时期最痴迷的电视剧
For him the show serves as a sort of wish fulfillment.
这个节目某种程度上满足了他的愿望
With each episode presenting the characters with new adventures that Hirsch wish he could have had when he was younger.
每集都描述了角色们的新奇冒险 正是Hirsch小时候自己所希望的
Hirsch was adamant in the writers room that Mabel was not dumb.
Hirsch坚持认为Mabel并不笨
She just likes to mess with people and have fun.
她只是很皮
And she isn't worried about what others think of her.
同时不是很在意别人对她的印象
Hirsch did say Mabel's storylines were more difficult to write.
Hirsch确实说过Mabel的故事更难撰写
As their source of conflict comes from the clash between her fantasy world and the real world.
因为Mabel故事中的矛盾冲突往往总是来自她的幻想世界和现实世界之间
The character has to learn that she won't always get what she wants.
Mabel需要知道她总是无法随心所欲
and she has to balance her expectations with reality.
同时必须把期待值降低到现实中来
Hirsch had some pretty deep and resonant notes in Gravity Falls
Hirsch给怪诞小镇写过一些能引起人共鸣且深刻的笔记
and it makes sense that he did initially plan to write kids animation.
这合情合理 因为这部动画一开始也并不打算做成一部儿童动画
He started his work on the kids series only after Disney approached him to pitch what would become Gravity Falls.
只有当迪士尼找到他做怪诞小镇之后 他才开始儿童动画的工作
The Simpsons were a huge comedic influence for Hirsch growing up
辛普森对Hirsch小时候的喜剧影响非常大
and showed him that animation could be as funny and smart as live-action television.
让他了解到动画也可以和电视剧一样机智有趣
Hirsch considered season 1 of the show to be an experiment.
Hirsch认为动画的第一季是实验品
I wrote most of the serialized story action into the background to keep the central plot episodic.
我把绝大部分的连续性的剧情写入到（次要的）背景当中 好让每集的主要剧情单元化
Season 2 picked up on the groundwork late in the first season
第二季接手了第一季的准备工作
and came out with a more grounded and serialized art.
并推出了更有逻辑更连续性的作品
Hirsch usually watched fans reactions as new episodes would air.
Hirsch常常在播放后观看粉丝的反应
but during the series finale he took a nap.
但是最后一集的时候他好好地休息了一下
When he woke up he checked Twitter and was pleased with the overwhelmingly positive responses.
当他醒来时 他查看推特的反应 并为压倒性的好评而感到满意
A real-life Journal 3 was released July 26th 2016 written by Alex Hirsch
日志3的实体书在2016年7月26日发布
and supervising producer/story editor Robbins Eddie.
由Alex Hirsch和动画的监督或者说是编剧Robbins Eddie编写
The real-life Journal 3 contains notes from Dipper and Mabel
日志3包含了Dipper和Mabel的笔记
as well as new pages filled with monsters and secrets never seen on the show.
与此同时还有动画中从未出现过的怪物和秘密
There's even a special edition of the Journal that shows extra content
同时还有一种日志的特殊版本包含
be viewed on the pages with a blacklight.
能在紫外光下看见额外的内容
Twin Peaks' received one last shout out in the series finale when Kyle MacLachlan voiced the bus driver
双峰相关的梗在动画中最后一次出现是在最后一集中由Kyle MacLachlan配音的巴士司机
that takes Mabel and Dipper home.
就是那个带着Mabel和Dipper回家的
Hirsch always wanted to have MacLachlan on the show
一直以来Hirsch都想邀请MacLachlan来动画客串
but could never find the right part.
但总是没找到好的方法
So when the end was near, Hirsch sent the actor a letter explaining
所以当大结局来临时 Hirsch给这个演员写了封信解释
how Dipper and Mabel are in many ways children of Twin Peaks.
这封信是说明Dipper和Mabel有多么像双峰中的小孩
And that would make sense for agent Cooper to be the one that takes them home.
这样 让特工Cooper带他们回家才是合情合理的
Though it was never set on the show,
尽管动画中从未出现过
Gravity Falls Journal 3 revealed that Dippers real name is Mason.
怪诞小镇的日志3中出现了Dipper的真名 Mason
According to the official Journal 3 at the end of the summer,
根据日志3 在暑假的最后
Journal one through three were tossed into the bottomless pit,
日志1到3被扔到了无底洞里
which may or may not be a wormhole but who knows if that's really the end of them.
也许并不是虫洞 但也可能就是这些日志的结局
Stan and Ford have a younger brother named Shermy.
Stan和阿福有一个弟弟叫Shermy
注:
此处应该是paternal 根据gravityfalls.wikia.com/wiki/List_of_unseen_characters中的原文 是paternal
Shermy Pines is Mabel and Dipper is parental grandfather.
Shermy Pines就是Mabel和Dipper的爷爷
Hirsch confirmed that millions of years ago the entire bullshit's Valley of Gravity Falls
Hirsch确认家百万年以前 怪诞小镇那个瞎扯的峡谷
was formed when a UFO crashed into the cliffs around the town and landed.
其实是UFO撞向城镇旁边的悬崖并着陆造成的
So the town's people have bumped into little pieces of the UFO over time.
所以随着时间的推移 小镇上的居民应该都见过UFO的碎片
It's one of the many reasons why the town is such an unusual place.
这也是为什么重力泉小镇是如此怪诞
In season one Hirsch originally outlined in episode the parody of the film Labyrinth starring the late David Bowie.
第一季中Hirsch略述了致敬了由David Bowie主演的电影魔幻迷宫的一集剧情
In the episode the Twins Went Labyrinth, Dipper keeps making fun of the movie.
本来在有一集双胞胎勇闯迷宫中 Dipper一直在开这个电影的玩笑
So Mabel asked the king of the goblins to take him away.
所以Mabel要求小妖精的首领把他带走
There's also a subplot where it's revealed Dipper only hates the movie because he's scared a puppet.
同样也有一个小细节透露了Dipper仅仅因为害怕木偶而讨厌这个电影
Sadly the Disney execs thought young kids would'nt get the references.
不幸地是迪士尼的高层认为小孩子看不懂这个剧情
注:
出自S2E04
Interestingly enough, in Sock Opera Dipper has no problem with the sock puppets.
足够有趣的是 Sock Opera那集中 Dipper并不害怕袜子做的木偶
Maybe he got over his fear?
也许他克服了自身的恐惧
In Weirdmageddon One there's a scene where Dipper and Wendy are driving through weirdness bubbles.
在Weirdmageddon One 那集 有一幕是Dipper和Wendy坐车穿越奇怪的泡泡
They briefly become live-action versions of themselves
他们曾短暂地变身为自己的真人配音演员
played by their real-life voice actor counterpart Jason Ritter and Linda Cardellini.
也就是Jason Ritter和Linda Cardellini
In the series finale, Bill was originally going to sing a song about everything he do when he exits the rift.
最后一集里 Bill本来要唱一首歌来讲述他离开裂缝以后要做的事
Hirsch said that they started writing the musical number but cut it when they realized there wasn't enough time.
Hirsch说 他们本来要开始写这段音乐了 但是被终止了 因为时间不够
The zodiac shown and hinted at throughout the series
黄道十二宫在剧中出现
was revealed in Weirdmageddon 3: Take Back The Falls to be a mystical human energy circuit
泄露了Weirdmageddon 3: Take Back The Falls 那集里会有神秘的人类能量回路
that can generate a force strong enough to defeat Bill.
能产生足够强的能量来打败Bill
Each character represents a symbol on the zodiac in Weirdmageddon 3.
每个角色都代表了黄道十二宫中的一个标志在Weirdmageddon 3 那集里
Dipper is a pine tree due to his hat.
由于帽子上的图案 Dipper对应的是松树
Mabel is a shooting star because the first sweaters.
因为第一次穿的毛衣的图案 Mabel是流星
Gideon is the pentacle because he has the symbol on his cape and the Tent of Telepathy.
Gideon是五角星 因为他的披风和通灵帐篷上有这个标志
Soos is the question mark because of his shirt.
Soos因为衣服上的图案而对应着问号
Ford is a six fingered hand because of his polydactyly.
阿福因为他的多指畸形而对应六根手指的手
Robbie is a stitched heart due to his hoodie which he's had since the seventh grade.
Robbie对应的是带缝线的心 因为这是他七年级以后一直穿着的连帽衫上的图案
Pacifica is the llama seen on the sweater she borrows from Mabel.
Pacifica对应着那件她从Mabel那里借来的毛衣上的羊驼图案
And Stan is the fish-like symbol because of his fez.
因为红圆帽上的图案 Stan对应着鱼形标志
Some of the symbols are more metaphorical
有些标志带有一定隐喻
like the spectacles representing the scholarly old man Mcgucket.
譬如眼镜代表了有学问的长者Mcgucket
And Wendy is ice because she's cool and calm in the face of danger.
而Wendy因为面对危险时的沉着冷静而对应着冰块
Ford and Stan finally get to fulfill their childhood dream of sailing around the world mentioned in A Tale of Two Stans.
阿福和Stan最终完成了他们童年时坐船周游世界的梦想 这个梦想出自S2E12那集A Tale of Two Stans.
An early sketch of Mabel included headgear
Mabel的早期版本包括需要头戴的箍牙
but Hirsch decided against it thinking would obscure her face too much.
但是Hirsch拒绝了这个方案 因为这会使她的脸看不清楚
吐槽:
从片名看出这里应该就是千与千寻的梗 宫崎骏律师函预警
Mabel's favorite anime movie is The Cranky Girl Who Did Chores in Spirit Town.
Mabel最爱的电影是奇怪的女孩做自己想象中的镇子上的杂物事
And she's seen it over 82 times almost as many times as I have seen Spirited Away.
她看了超过82次 几乎和我看千与千寻 的次数一样多
Gideon was partially inspired by a child psychic Hirsch's mother saw on TV.
Gideon这个人设有部分最初由Hirsch妈妈在电视上看到的一个通灵小孩所启发
Hirsch felt like he would be a suitable and entertaining rival for Stan.
Hirsch认为他将是Stan的合适且有趣的竞争对手
Mabel, Dipper and Stan have all been in the county jail thanks to one of Stan's family fun days
在某次Stan的家庭快乐日中 Mabel Dipper和Stan被关到了县监狱里
but only Stan has been to jail in Columbia.
不过只有Stan坐过哥伦比亚的监狱
If they wants to travel anywhere he's limited to cars, boats and trains,
如果他们想四处游玩 他只能坐车 船和火车
he was banned from airplanes after petitioning to get July 13th banned from the calendar.
Stan被禁止搭乘航班因为他之前请愿在日历上取消7月13日
Hirsch said he pictures Pacifica getting a job at Greasy's Diner
Hirsch说他曾画过一张Pacifica在Greasy's Diner工作的画面
and working with Lazy Susan after her family loses Northwest Manor.
也就是在她家里失去Northwest大宅之后和懒Susan工作
注:
根据配图和片名 这里指的应该是EVA 痞子律师函预警
Soos's favorite anime is Neon Crisis Revelations Angry Cute Girl: Annihilation.
Soos's最爱的动画是 霓虹灯危机揭露了愤怒可爱女孩: 消失
注:
应该指的是这个毒舌配音系列av514500
It's a good pic but I wonder if he prefers the dubbed version.
这听起来不错 但是我更好奇他是不是更喜欢配音版
Journal 2 contains information on how to summon Bill Cipher
日志2包含了如何召唤Bill Cipher的内容
while Journal 3 has instructions on how to stop Bill if he is summoned.
而日志3则介绍了如何干掉已被召唤的Bill
Smart-thinking Ford.
阿福真聪明
Bill's original concept art had him as green instead of his iconic yellow.
Bill最初的设定主体色是绿色而不是现在这个标志性黄色
He was eventually switched to the latter after his green body look too much like a leaf.
因为绿色看起来太像树叶 于是他最终变成了后者的颜色 黄色
Bill is like really really old.
Bill似乎非常年长
He claims to be older than time or the universe which would make him about 13.8 Billion cosmological years old.
他声称他比时空都要老 意味着他可能有138亿年也就是宇宙那么老
He doesn't look a day over 30 to me.
但是我觉得他就像刚出生不到30天的孩子
It's revealed that Bill is actually from the second dimension.
这透露了Bill可能来自二次元
This might be a reference to the fact that Gravity Falls itself is a 2d animated show.
毕竟这是个二次元动画
What do ancient Egyptians, George Washington and Stanley Kubrick have in common?
古埃及人 乔治·华盛顿和斯坦利·库布里克之间有什么共同点吗
They've all been enlisted by Bill to build this portal.
他们都被Bill争取去建造这个传送门
注:
参见油管视频Alex & Dana Charity Draw-A-Thon
It was confirmed by Hirsch during a Charity Draw-A-Thon that Deputy Durland and Sheriff Blubs are a couple.
在一次慈善性质的绘画马拉松上 Hirsch确认了Deputy Durland和Sheriff Blubs是一对cp
The Mystery Shack was originally the home of Ford Pines
神秘小屋最初是阿福的家
and he lived there during his studies of Gravity Falls.
他在研究重力泉小镇的时候住在里面
It was only after his brother had disappeared that Stan moved into the shack
而Stan是在阿福小时之后才住了进来
and turned it into the Mystery Shack in order to pay for its rent.
同时为了付得起租金 把小屋变成神秘小屋招揽客人
But before it was the Mystery Shack,
但是在变为神秘小屋之前
the ramshackle house was called the Murder Hut when it first opened.
这个破败的房子在刚开张的时候也被称为杀手小屋
Shit Stan, glad you lightened up.
可见Stan变得开朗了起来 让人很高兴
Have you ever wondered what happened to Giffany or is it Jiffaney.
你曾想过Giffany或者说Jiffaney后来变得怎么样了
Either way don't worry. She's not dead.
不过不必担心 她并没有死
Hirsch confirmed at BigFest 2016 in the Gravity Falls Journal 3 that she's still alive somewhere.
Hirsch在2016年的BigFest确认在日志3中会写道她还在某处活着
Manley Dan was called Boyish Dan when he was a boy.
Manley Dan小时候曾被叫做Boyish Dan
So I wonder if that means he'll be called Old Man Dan when he's old.
我现在在想他老了以后会不会被叫做长者Dan
Wendy's father makes her and her brothers trained for the apocalypse during Christmas.
Wendy的父亲要求她和她的兄弟在圣诞节期间为末日训练
You got to be prepared, even during the most wonderful time of the year.
就算是一年中最美好的时光也需要拿来准备
注:
出自S1E03
Mabel and Dipper make fake IDs so they can get into the bar downtown in the episode Headhunters.
Mabel和Dipper伪造了身份证件 这样他们便能在Headhunters那集中进入市中心的吧里
Their fake names are Sir Dippinsauce and Lady Mapleton, age 45 and 21.
他们的假身份是45岁的蘸酱先生和21岁的梅宝子女士
In The Inconveniencing, Mabel's hallucination dolphin, Aoshima was named after Gravity Falls director Johnny Aoshima.
在The Inconveniencing 那集中 Mabel's幻觉中的海豚青岛 名字来源于怪诞小镇的导演Johnny Aoshima
Onward Aoshima!
前进吧Aoshima
吐槽:
吹一波Dipper x Tyrone和No.3 x No.4
Dipper's clones number three and number four disappear after they ride off with Robbie's bicycle at the end of Double Dipper.
在Double Dipper 那集的最后 Dipper的克隆体3号和4号在偷走Robbie的自行车后消失了
They get one last appearance and the end credits of Weirdmageddon 3: Take Back The Falls.
在Weirdmageddon 3: Take Back The Falls 的片尾制作名单片段中 他们最后一次出现
Mabel is able to wear nachos as earrings with the help of some very sticky nacho cheese.
Mabel把奶酪玉米片当作耳环来佩戴 得益于那粘力十分强大的奶酪
I'm jealous.
我有点嫉妒了
In Irrational Treasure Mabel and Dipper discover that the Northwest cover-up document
在Irrational Treasure 那集中 Mabel和Dipper发现了Northwest的隐藏文件
also states that Thomas Jefferson was actually just two kids in an overcoat standing on each other's shoulders
声称Thomas Jefferson不过是两个小孩 一个站在肩膀上撑起来形成的大衣
吐槽:
EVA亚当:
喵喵喵？
and an enormous evil time devouring baby from another dimension is frozen an Antarctic glacier.
而来自另一个次元的巨大邪恶时空吞噬宝宝被封印在了南极冰川里
And I bet that's just the tip of the iceberg.
我猜是冰山的顶部
The pixel sprites and Fight Fighters were animated by Paul Robertson who is known for Scott Pilgrim vs. the World, the game and the feds(?).
像素精灵和Fight Fighters 那集由Paul Robertson导演 他因Scott Pilgrim vs. the World那部游戏和电影出名
In the cold open of Summerween Mabel and Dipper pass a shelf of masks
在Summerween那集的开场 Mabel和Dipper路过了一书架的面具
which are actually the faces of crude work on the show.
大致就是节目组工作人员的脸
Look closely and you'll see Johnny Aoshima, Eric Fountain and Matt Brawley.
仔细看你会发现Johnny Aoshima Eric Fountain和Matt Brawley
When Mabel receives messages and bottles from her Mermando in The Deep End.
在The Deep End 那集中 当Mabel收到Mermando的消息和瓶子的时候
One of the bottles says LEBAM which is her name backwards.
有一个瓶子写着LEBAM 恰好是她名字单词的逆序
Maybe that's how they spelled things under the sea?
也许这就是他们海底人拼单词的习惯吧
注:
出自S1E19
Before going to fight the bat in the kitchen in the Dreamscaperers,
在Dreamscaperers 那集和厨房里的蝙蝠对战之前
Dipper picks up a spoon in a saucepan which are both nicknames for the constellation the Big Dipper.
Dipper拿起了一个深平底锅中的勺子 而这两者都是北斗七星的昵称
And Mabel sunset sweater in the Dreamscaperers was meant to represent the show's transition from a light to dark series.
Mabel在Dreamscaperers 中穿着的日落毛衣意味着动画将由较为光明的剧情转而踏入黑暗的部分
注:
出自S2E04
In Sock Opera, Soos and Stan's puppets are both made from paper bags rather than socks.
在Sock Opera 那集中 Soos和Stan的木偶都由纸盒做成 而不是袜子
E-for-effort, Stan.
Stan 你还需要更加努力啊
The VHS, Clash of the Genres is rated O for old people.
冲突流派的录像带评级是O 意味着老年人观看
注:
出自S2E06
Little Gift Shop of Horrors originally had a twist ending where the visiting tourist was revealed to be M. Night Shyamalan.
Little Gift Shop of Horrors 最初有一个转折性结局 就是造访的游客的身份是M·奈特·沙马兰
注:
出自S2E08
It's revealed in Blendin's Game that Soos lives on "Chambrot Drive"
在Blendin's Game 那集中 透露出来Soos住在Chambrot Drive
which is a shout out to Hirsch friend and inspiration for the character Jesus Chambrot.
这是致敬了Hirsch的朋友 同时也是Soos角色的灵感Jesus Chambrot
Ford may have more than just the three Journals we've seen.
Ford也许有着不止3本日志
注:
出自S2E15
In The Last Mabelcorn, Ford's dream contains red and blue Journals
在The Last Mabelcorn 那集中 阿福梦见了红色和蓝色的日志
with yellow six fingered hands on the covers
而这些日志上面都有六指印记
as well as a brown Journal with a yellow triangle on the front.
同时还有一部棕色的日志 封面是一个黄色三角形
Weirdmageddon Part One is the only full-length episode of the series where Mabel does not speak.
Weirdmageddon Part One 是Mabel完全没有说话的一集
If the opening theme of Weirdmageddon One is reversed Bill is heard saying I'm watching you nerds.
如果反向播放Weirdmageddon One 的OP 能听见Bill在说 我正在看着你们 书呆子们
Hirsch said that the second half of season 2 covered the plot that was originally planned for season 3.
Hirsch说第二季的下半部分的剧情本来是计划用于制作第三季
Ever wonder if Quentin Trembley, America's favorite lost president
想过美国最著名的失踪总统Quentin Trembley
had more of a backstory?
有着更丰富的背景故事没有
Hirsch wish he had more time to include all of his thoughts and theories about Trembley significance with the scope of the show.
Hirsch希望能在动画中有更多的时间来说明Trembley重要性的思想和理论
Stan was married to a woman named Marilyn but she divorced him after being married for only six hours.
Stan曾经娶过一个叫Marilyn的女人 但是仅仅六个小时后就和他离婚了
Hirsch's grandfather named Stan also had a wife named Marilyn.
Hirsch的爷爷Stan也有一个叫Marilyn的妻子
According to Bill Cipher the worst feel he ever made involves banking with a man named Thomas J Beale.
根据Bill Cipher的说法 他最糟的体验是和Thomas J Beale去银行存钱
He also mentions that the ominous being
他同样也谈到了那个不祥之物
注:
出自av11835785的P3
on the other side of the mailbox is a real blabbermouth.
也就是邮箱的另一边是真正的嘴巴不严的人
In Gravity Falls Journal 3 goes to read from yeah not so a deadly
在日志3中的文章 语气一开始是没那么坏
to demonic vengeance specter which is real bad.
到恶魔复仇幽灵是真的糟糕
The time baby can be easily distracted by jingling keys
时间宝宝很容易被叮当铃分神
which Hirsch mentioned in the in Between the Pines special.
而Hirsch在Between the Pines 特典中提到了这件事
注:
出自S2E13
The Infinity sided dice was brought back by Ford from another dimension.
无穷面骰子是由阿福从另一个维度带来的东西
It's currently locked in the underground laboratory for safekeeping.
现在被所在地下实验室保管了起来
In the series finale, Stan Pines retires and gives ownership of the Mystery Shack to Soos.
在动画的最后一集里 Stan Pines退休了 并把神秘小屋交给了Soos
Hirsch has said his dream would have been to make a Gravity Falls feature film
Hirsch说他的梦想是制作一个怪诞小镇电影
and at one point Disney discussed it with him.
迪士尼曾有次和他讨论过这个问题
In the end they decided the show wasn't big enough to warrant it
最后他们决定这个动画还不足够大 不值得去做一部电影
but Hirsch said if someone would give him fifty million dollars he'd make of Gravity Falls movie.
但是Hirsch说 如果有人给他5000万美元 他肯定做
Come on guys let's get that Kickstarter going.
大家快快来众筹吧
Gravity Falls was nominated for choice TV animated show
Gravity Falls被提名为电视动画之选奖项
at the Teen Choice Awards every year from 2013 to 2016.
在2013年到2016年每年的少年之选奖的评选中
Gravity Falls was nominated for an Emmy in 2014 and 2015
怪诞小镇在2014年和2015年被提名艾美奖
for outstanding individual achievement in animation.
就是艾美奖中的动画节目最佳个人成就奖
Ian Worrel won for Dreamscaperers and Alonso Ramirez Ramos won for Not What He Seems.
Ian Worrel因Dreamscaperers 那集获奖 而Alonso Ramirez Ramos则是Not What He Seems 那集
Hirsch had said that he remains open to continuing the series with additional episodes or a special
Hirsch曾说过他对通过特典的方式延续动画的想法持开放态度
since there are a couple more characters and plots he'd like to revisit someday.
因为有些剧情和角色他很想再回味一遍
注:
根据美亚的预订页面http://a.co/6RHL18W 全集BD和DVD将于2018年7月24日发售
While Gravity Falls has yet to release full seasons on DVD,
虽然怪诞小镇尚未发布全集DVD
there are two featurette DVDs that contain episodes from the first season.
已经发布过第一季的两集短片的DVD
In February 2016 Disney XD released Take Back the Falls,
在2016年2月 Disney XD发布了游戏Take Back the Falls
a game is so develop on the watch Disney XD mobile app.
一个研发在Disney XD观看应用上的游戏
In the game the user could either be Mabel or Dipper
在游戏里玩家可以选择Mabel或Dipper
and play through the events the Weirdmageddon 3: Take Back The Falls.
同时打通Weirdmageddon 3: Take Back The Falls 那集中的剧情
The message at the end of the theme song in the series finale read backwards says,
最后那集ED的倒放信息是
Goodbye Gravity Falls.
再见怪诞小镇
The series of Gravity Falls takes place from June to September 1st 2012.
怪诞小镇系列故事发生的时间始自2012年的6月至9月1日
Now that is one long summer.
现在看来真是一段漫长的暑假
Once again I'm Alyssa
再说一次 我是Alyssa
and thanks for watching 107 more more facts about Gravity Falls.
谢谢大家收看这集关于怪诞小镇的107个更多更多的事实
Would you want to see a movie?
你想看怪诞小镇的电影吗
Are you sad that the endless summer finally ended?
你对这个无尽暑假的终结感到惋惜吗
Comment below and let us know.
到油管评论区评论让我们知道
Don't forget to click the bell icon to become part of the notification squad.
别忘了点击钟形图标成为通知队列的一员
We have video shopping every day so make sure to subscribe.
我们日更 所以别忘了订阅本频道
And remember Frederator loves you.
记住我们爱你